I have a very strong sense
of identity in my blindness.
One of the misconceptions that people
have about blind people is that we don't
care about how we look or the way
we present ourselves to the world.
The Ray-Ban Meta Glasses allows me
to still look fashionable and be able
to do the tasks that I need
done as a blind person.
- Hey, Meta
call a volunteer with Be My Eyes.
- Calling a volunteer.
- Hey there. How can I help?
- Hi, I just got a new record player and I
wanted to see if you could help me figure
out which of these buttons turns it on.
- Absolutely. I think it's the one on the bottom.
Try that.
- This one here?
- Yeah, that's it.
- Perfect. Thank you.
- Being able to connect with a human
through the Be My Eyes Call feature makes
a world of difference.
- How can I help?
- Hi, I'm going to a salsa night
later today...
- I'm able to ask follow-up questions and get
more detailed information.
- Try the next one. Found it.
- The benefits to using Be My Eyes
through the glasses is being able to be
hands-free. As somebody that uses a cane,
I love being independent. That
makes a huge difference.
- Hi, I was wondering if you could just give
me a spot check to see if I missed anything.
- Yes, I'm taking a look. You
look amazing. It looks perfect.
- Oh, thank you so much.
- I'm already like a very active,
extroverted person and I
feel like the glasses help me
be able to be that even more.
I think the Ray-Ban Meta Glasses will
make a huge difference in people being
able to use the tools that they need to
live the lives that they want to live.